Hello, welcome to Open Tierra.
Today we're looking at Singapore,
a dynamic city -state known for its
impressive skyline cultural diversity and world -renowned attractions such as Marina Bay Sands and Gardens by the Bay.
Join us to find out more about Singapore's
geography,
people, food,
and history.
Singapore is an island city -state located
off the southern tip of the Malay Peninsula in Southeast Asia.
With a total land area of only 719.1
km2 or 277 km2 it is one of the smallest
countries in the world.
Yet Singapore is also one of the most
densely populated countries with over 5 million people living on the main island.
Singapore consists of one main island and
over 60 smaller islands.
The main island is linked by bridges to
peninsula Malaysia in the north.
To the south lies Indonesia and the Riau
Islands.
With limited land, Singapore has had to
maximize land usage through careful urban planning.
Singapore has little variation in terrain
due to its small size.
The terrain consists mostly of sedimentary
rock and granite.
The main island has a number of low hills,
including Bukit Timah, one of the highest
points.
Singapore's coastline has dramatically
changed over the years through extensive land reclamation projects.
Several rivers flow from the center of the
island towards the coastlines.
Due to rapid development,
most of Singapore's original mangrove
swamps and rainforests no longer exist.
However,
efforts have been made to preserve the
country's remaining natural greenery.
As one of the most densely populated
places on earth,
Singapore has creatively managed its
limited space through innovative urban planning.
High -rise residential complexes house
most of the population.
The city is divided into broad regions,
such as the central business district,
renowned for its skyscrapers.
Singapore is also known for its extensive
green urban spaces and nature reserves that seamlessly integrate with the metropolis.
The country is steadily reclaiming land
from the sea to expand the main island.
Singapore is one of the most densely
populated countries in the world, with a population of around 5.6
million according to the World Bank.
According to the 2020 census,
the majority of Singaporeans are
ethnically Chinese at around 74% of the population.
Next are Malays at 13.5
% followed by Indians at 9%.
The remainder are mostly Eurasian and
other minority groups.
Singapore has four official languages,
English, Mandarin, Chinese,
Malay and Tamil.
English is the language for business and
government.
Most Singaporeans are bilingual and speak
English, plus one other official language like Chinese,
Malay or Tamil.
The major religions practiced in Singapore
are Buddhism,
Christianity,
Islam,
Taoism and Hinduism.
Buddhism and Taoism are predominantly
followed by the Chinese population.
Islam is practiced by the Malay community,
while most Indians adhere to Hinduism.
About 18% of Singaporeans identify as non
-religious.
Here are a few iconic dishes that every
visitor must try in Singapore.
Hainanese chicken rice is considered
Singapore's national dish.
It consists of fragrant rice and boneless
chicken,
seasoned with ginger and soy sauce.
The chicken is poached to produce tender
meat and flavorful broth.
It's often served with chili sauce on the
side.
Laksa is a creamy, spicy coconut curry
noodle soup.
There are different variations,
but the Katong style is popular in
Singapore.
It contains thick vermicelli,
shrimp,
fish cakes and boiled eggs in a rich
coconut broth with spices.
Laksa is a perfect comfort food for rainy
days.
Nasi lemak is a Malay rice dish wrapped in
banana leaves.
It consists of fragrant coconut rice
served with fried anchovies,
peanuts,
egg and chili sambal.
Optional sides include fried chicken
wings, cucumber slices,
fish cake and onion omelette.
Nasi Biryani is an Indian inspired rice
dish that's aromatic and colourful.
Spiced basmati rice is layered and cooked
with chicken,
fish or mutton, raisins, saffron cashews
and curry leaves add more flavour.
Strategically located along major sea
trade routes,
Singapore has long served as an important
port and commercial centre in Southeast Asia.
The earliest known settlements in
Singapore date back to the 2nd century CE.
The island was located on trade routes
between India and China and was referred to as Temasek, meaning sea town in Javanese.
From the 14th to early 19th century,
Singapore was part of the Malaka Sultanate
and then the Johor Sultanate.
During this time, a small fishing village
emerged at the mouth of the Singapore River.
In 1819,
British statesmen Sir Thomas Stamford
Raffles established a British port on the island.
The port formally became a British colony
in 1824.
Under British rules, Singapore grew into a
major hub for regional and international trade.
Immigrants from China, India and the Malay
Archipelago flocked to Singapore.
Its population and economic importance
expanded enormously during the colonial era.
From 1942 to 1945,
Japan occupied Singapore during World War
II.
The British surrender marked their largest
military defeat.
During the occupation, Singapore was
renamed Sionan.
The Japanese occupation ended after the
war in 1945.
Singapore then briefly became part of the
British military administration before returning to colonial rule.
After the war,
Singapore progressively moved towards self
-governance.
The People's Action Party won the first
general election under full internal self -government in 1959.
On August 9, 1965,
Singapore declared independence from
Britain and merged with Malaya, Sabah and Sarawak to form Malaysia.
However, due to political and economic
disputes,
Singapore left Malaysia and became fully
independent on August 9, 1965.
Under Prime Minister Lee Kuan Yew,
Singapore rapidly industrialized and became a global financial hub.
Strict laws and efficient government
supported economic development.
Today,
Singapore is one of the four Asian tigers,
a highly developed and high -income
country.
It is a global leader in finance,
education, technology,
trade and transportation.
This covers some key events in Singapore's
transformative history.
Over the past 50 years,
Singapore has rapidly grown into one of
the world's most prosperous nations.
Its strategic location,
stable government, skilled workforce and
pro -business policies have made Singapore a global commerce, finance and transport hub.
As of 2022,
its GDP is around $460 billion,
according to World Bank data.
Since independence in 1965,
Singapore has transformed from a low
-income nation into a developed free market economy.
The government promoted foreign investment
and exports in the manufacturing and services sectors.
Singapore also focused on education to
develop a highly skilled workforce.
Strategic economic policies and efficient
governance have enabled Singapore's impressive economic growth over the decades.
Singapore excels in several key sectors,
including electronics,
chemicals,
financial services,
tourism,
transportation and logistics.
It is a leading world facilitating re
-exports.
Manufacturing, oil refining and business
services are also major contributors to its GDP.
Singapore aims to grow innovative
industries like biomedicine and digital technology.
Some of Singapore's competitive advantages
include its corruption -free business environment,
strategic location and transport
infrastructure,
minimal regulation and multilingual
workforce.
It also has close trade ties with major
economies like China, India and Indonesia.
Intellectual property protection,
advanced digital connectivity and high
productivity further strengthen its economy.
Its strategic location along historic
trade routes and diverse immigrant population have contributed to Singapore's rich cultural landscape.
Each main ethnic group in Singapore has
its own unique culture.
Malay culture is rooted in traditions,
arts and poetry from Southeast Asia.
Indian culture brings colorful festivals,
spicy cuisine,
movies and arts.
Chinese culture contributes to lunar new
year celebrations,
dialects, philosophical traditions and
architectural influences.
Yet Singaporean culture is also distinct
from the cultural practices of China,
India and Malaysia.
Performing arts have grown in popularity
in multi -cultural Singapore.
The Esplanade is its National Performing
Arts Centre.
Literature often explores Singaporean
society and identity through various languages.
Singapore's film industry produces popular
Singaporean films.
Media is closely monitored by the
government which also aims to preserve the four official languages.
If you enjoyed this video on Singapore,
you'll love this next one.