Oh, what are you guys in for?
Bank robbery.
Drug trafficking.
What about you?
Movie piracy.
Who was?
People in show business work hard to make those movies.
My media stocks underperform because of people like you.
My brother lost his job as a grip on a movie set because of piracy.
He had to sell his jet ski.
A grip without a jet ski ain't no grip at all.
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
Oh, you're about to find out what we do to copyright infringers.
We do to copyright infringers.
And then threaten litigation against accused infringers.
We didn't infringe on anything.
People don't wanna hurt us like that.
In times like that you can put your ass down here.
Why are you crafting a boss?
Leave me behind too!
Get you crap!
That's not what I'm going to do.
Woohoo!
It's almost like having Dad here.
Only with less groundling when I go near his food.
I just want to know who dropped the dime on Dad.
Lousy Rat.
Maybe the person that turned your father in
thought they were doing the right thing.
Homer just pirated a movie.
It's not the worst thing Dad ever did.
It's not even the worst kind of pirate Dad's ever been.
Lisa, tell your brother that stealing is wrong.
No matter what.
I don't know.
It wasn't like Dad was stealing for himself.
He created this wonderful experience for the whole town.
I just can't imagine anyone turning him in.
Hey!
You got it!
What are you doing out of prison?
You have to go back and give yourself up.
I can't go back to jail.
There's no shampoo.
Just soap.
Wait, I know one place in Springfield
that doesn't care about internet piracy laws.
Thanks for taking us in.
Our family always appreciates asylum.
Refugee seeking asylum.
He deserves asylum.
This country that is like being on Swedish soil.
You're a safe here as you would be in the Skata Skrapan.
Your country doesn't think a legal download in movies is wrong.
The people at Sweden believe all movies should be shared freely.
How was that Matt's deal?
Your Hollywood studios are the real thieves.
Claiming all their hit movies have lost money.
I spit on their bookkeeping.
Yeah, and why don't they make a sequel to Taken
where the hangover guys get taken
and the only ones that can rescue them is Fast and Furious?
Man, I would love to pirate that.
As would the proud people of Sweden.
They found us.
There's only one sure far away to get fugitives out of a foreign building.
Blasting death metal.
Respecting the law, respecting the law.
The copyright law, copyright law.
Copyright law.
You like this?
Swedes love death metal.
It reminds us of death.
Damn those peace prize-giving fish smokers.
I'm so tired of being trapped in this embassy.
Consulate. Consulates are regional offices
which serve the embassy in the capital.
Thank you so much for sticking with me through all this.
You're the greatest wipe in the world.
It was me! I was the one who told the FBI!
How could you? You're my own flesh and blood!
I was just trying to do the right thing.
Who would have thought the authorities would use a confession against me?
Which authorities?
The FBI.
To import authority, airport authority,
to import authority,
airport authority,
to...
Have you forgotten what you promised that are wedding?
To love and cherish, to aid in a bet?
I never wanted to say funny vows.
Well, you did! And they got laughs!
Sell it, laughs!
I didn't mean for this to happen, but you were stealing.
All I ever had was you looking up for me.
I got nothing now.
All rise, the matter of the people versus Homer Simpson.
The people call High-Want-Ultra-Predosa Judd Apatown.
Homer Simpson is an enemy of art.
Art created by writers, directors,
and the guy who uses a computer to erase or enhance nipples.
And not just the people who dream for a living,
but the people who depend on us,
the spin-class instructors,
the personal rabbis, Seth Rogan.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
It's true, I need him.
I saw a bootleg DVD of the 40-year-old virgin
for sale at a car wash.
They left off my director's commentary.
It didn't even have a blooper reel!
Homer Simpson, you have been found guilty
of illegal reproduction and distribution of copyrighted material.
The illegal reproduction and distribution of copyrighted material.
Well-faw distribution marketing schedule, I gave you...
I just handled distribution.
Before sentencing, do you have anything to say for yourself?
No.
Oh, no, tell them you're side of the story!
I know I heard you, but please, trust me now.
It'll work!
You know what, Judge Epitow?
I do have something to say.
These movie people may say I'm a pirate,
but I'm just a man, a man who loved Hollywood too much.
So I made my own rules,
and fought the big guys who tried to destroy my way of life.
He doesn't sound like a villain.
He sounds like a classic underdog.
He's the unlikeliest of heroes!
But where's the love story?
At first, my wife didn't believe in me.
Maybe we forgot why we fell in love in the first place.
But when time seemed darkest, one minute ago,
she was there,
and gave me the strength and courage to fight for what I believe in.
He's a downloading David versus a greedy Goliath!
An Aaron Brockovich!
But with more cleavage!
Two, three, good lord!
He's getting all four quadrants!
One family against all odds took on the system,
and lost.
Mr. Simpson, I'd like to buy the rights to make a movie based on your true story.
I'm attached to executive producer!
Executive decision!
Executive assistant!
Attached! Attached!
One movie! We envision a trilogy!
Wilson's family was to play your family.
I'd be Jaden!
I'm not Jaden!
On behalf of Hollywood, we are dropping all charges.
These people hate my dad.
How can they make a movie about him?
Hollywood may be run by big corporations trying to squash people,
but they make movies about people standing up to big corporations trying to squash them,
in winning.
I'll sign with whoever can convince Channing Tatum to gain the most weight to play me.
Surprise!
What the hell is all this?
We're so excited about your movie that we're having a special screening.
But the movie isn't in theaters till next week.
We ripped a version off bootleg bait just like you taught us.
It's still got time to go on it, but otherwise it's a clean copy.
You're pirating my movie?
Now how you are?
Piracy is stealing! You're taking money out of my family's mouths!
But the movie is... it's about you pirating movies!
Oh, that's Hollywood fantasy.
We live in the real world, where I have something called...
Profit, Participation!
That's negative, man.
Oh, me.
Now, all of you go see my movie in the theater the day it opens.
No bargain, Matt Nays.
And tell your friends it was great!
Why the stuff they advertise in the commercials before it?
Homer the movie, where it's Ask Body Spray.
And so should you!
Don't ask! Do smell!
Oh, my dear, we really think you should be.
Up, up, up, up.
Well, have we learned about that blindly supporting our husband?
Ask Body Spray!
The End
But then when time seemed darkest, she was there.
She gave me the strength and courage to fight for what I believe in.
On behalf of Hollywood, we're dropping all charges!
Yeah!
So what do you think, Lisa?
Who are the good guys here?
The media companies or the internet freedom guys?
Well, both groups claim their intentions are noble, but at the end of the day,
they're both trying to steal as much money as they can.
So, everyone's a pirate?
And the worst one of all is...
Music