Oh, look! There's five little ducks.
One, two, three, four, five little ducks went swimming one day
Over the hill and far away
Mother duck said, quack, quack, quack
But only four little ducks came back
One, two, three, four little ducks went swimming one day
Over the hill and far away
Mother duck said, quack, quack, quack
But only three little ducks came back
One, two, three little ducks went swimming one day
Over the hill and far away
Mother duck said, quack, quack, quack
But only two little ducks came back
One, two little ducks went swimming one day
Over the hill and far away
Mother duck said, quack, quack, quack
But only one little duck came back
One little duck went swimming one day
Over the hill and far away
Mother duck said, quack, quack, quack
But no little ducks came swimming back
Sad mother duck went out one day
Over the hill and far away
Sad mother duck said, quack, quack, quack
And all the five little ducks came back