What can I do for you?
Hello!
I might buy some notebooks.
What kind of notebooks would you like?
Composition or spiral?
I don't like spiral notebooks because the
spirals get all messed up.
So I'd like two composition notebooks.
Line notebooks or blank pages?
What do you prefer?
Line notebooks with margin please.
What size do you need?
I need a five size.
Okay, I have this one in good quality
paper and plus to cover.
There are five dollars each.
They look good.
I'll take them.
Okay, do you need anything else?
I would also like a set of blue gel
ballpoint pens, a pack of five pencils,
a pack of printer paper, a set of washable
markers, and a pair of scissors.
Can you please tell me how much is that
set of highlighters over there?
It's five dollars.
It's not expensive, so I'll take that too.
That'll be eighty five dollars.
There you go.
Hello!
How may I help you, sir?
I'm looking for a birthday present for my
wife.
Can you recommend something?
I think a necklace would be a great choice
for such an occasion.
That sounds like a very good idea.
I would like something simple, nothing too
fancy.
How about these necklaces over here?
I don't think these would fit her style.
They're too sophisticated.
Do you have more designs?
Yes, we have this gold necklace with the
circular pendant or this silver necklace with a little heart.
Wow,
this is exactly what I'm looking for.
How much is it?
Well, it's usually priced at $199,
but you're lucky.
Today it's 20% off.
Wonderful.
I'll take it.
And can you also recommend something for
my seven -year -old daughter?
Sure.
How about this headband?
It's $15.
I think she would love it.
I'll take it.
Okay, do you need anything else?
No, that's all.
Thank you.
Alright, I'll ring them up at the cash
register for you.
Excuse me.
I'd like to try this blouse on.
Can you show me where the feeding room is?
It's at the back, right next to the
dresses.
Please follow me.
Okay, thank you.
Does it fit you?
No, it's too large, actually.
Do you have it in a smaller size?
I need extra small.
I'll go check.
I'll be right back.
Here you are, extra small.
Thank you.
Is this one okay?
Yes, it fits perfectly, and I love this
style.
It also matches a skirt up just bought.
How much is it?
It's $29.
That's quite an affordable price for such
a high -quality blouse.
Yes, it's a stylish blouse, made with
soft, lightweight material.
It's a great choice for the hot summer
days.
We offer fashion and quality at the best
price.
Can I pay by credit card?
Yes, of course.
Alison, I don't know what to wear at
Malone's party.
It's going to be a house party, so I need
a cool casual outfit.
It shouldn't be that difficult.
You have so many stylish and trendy
clothes.
But I don't know what to choose and how to
match them for the best look.
I was thinking of wearing this blitted
skirt I bought last week.
What do you think about it?
I think it's out of fashion, and it's too
long and large.
It doesn't suit you.
It makes you look uncool.
I guess you're right.
Maybe it was a wrong choice.
What do you say about this high -waisted
jeans skirt?
It's actually very trendy, because high
-waist is in style now.
You think so?
Definitely.
We can add this big buckle belt.
Okay.
What actually I put on?
Let's pair it with this cropped long
sleeve white top.
It looks great.
I love this blouse because it features
that big sleeve trend.
This layered necklace pairs perfectly with
the top two.
What a wonderful idea.
It matches my new shoes.
You look smashing.
Hi.
I saw your shoe clearance sale add on the
flyer.
Yeah, we're offering discounts on all our
shoes.
It's the best chance to buy your favorite
shoes at a low price.
What are you interested in buying?
I need some comfortable shoes for running,
which shoes would be most suitable.
In my opinion, these sneakers would be
best for your needs.
They're great for running lots of miles,
and they're very comfortable.
I like their design.
How much are these sneakers?
Their regular price is $150,
but they're on sale for 50% off right now.
Wow, really?
Let me try them on.
Do you have a size 8?
Let me see.
Here you are.
You can go for a walk around the store.
They're soft and comfortable.
They slide off and on easily.
They fit me well.
I'll buy them.
Great.
I'll pack them up for you and you can pay
at the cash register.
Thank you for your help.
You're very welcome.
Excuse me, but I've lost my glasses
somewhere in this store about an hour ago.
I came back to search for them, but
couldn't find them.
Can you help me?
Sure thing.
Where exactly do you think you left them?
I left them at the sunglasses counter.
I was trying on sunglasses.
That's why I took them off.
They have quite narrow lenses.
So, small lenses then.
Right and their rectangular shaped, not
round.
And are the frames thick or thin?
Oh, very thin.
And their color is black.
I hope someone turns them in because I
really need them.
So, there are glasses with thin black
frames and rectangular lenses.
And you last saw them at the sunglasses
counter.
That's right.
All right.
Leave me your phone number and I'll call
you if someone turns them in.
Hello there.
How can I help you today?
I'm looking to upgrade to a bigger car
today.
My wife and I are expecting our third
child and we need a bit more space now.
I completely understand.
Are you thinking of a car or an SUV?
Or are you interested in a van?
I think we would like an SUV,
but one that isn't too big.
And we'd prefer something with decent gas
mileage.
We have a new hybrid SUV that might be
great for your family.
Take a look.
Wow, this is really nice.
It has leather interior, a backup camera,
video screens for the kids, and optional third -door seating.
Very nice.
How's the gas mileage?
It gets about 40 miles per gallon.
That's incredible.
That's better than my current car.
How much is it?
The price is $40,000.
Would you like to try it out?
Definitely.
Let's take it for a test drive.
What do you think?
It was great.
A smooth ride and very comfortable.
We have some great financing deals going
on right now.
Sounds good to me.
Let's talk out the details.
Awesome.
Let's head to my office.
Good morning.
What can I do for you?
My car is making a weird noise.
Tell me about the noise.
Is it squeaking, rumbling, knocking?
It's more like a squeaking.
And when does it generally happen?
It tends to happen when I'm stopping.
I'm going to take your car for a quick
diagnostic test to see if I can determine what is causing the sound.
Great.
Thanks.
It looks like you need new brakes.
The brake pads are worn down, so every
time you stop, the metal from the brakes cause a loud noise.
I can put new ones on today if you'd like.
That would be great.
Thank you.
I also noticed that your oil needs changed
and your spark plugs need replacing.
Would you like me to take care of those as
well?
I might as well fix everything while I'm
here.
I'll get everything running smoothly for
you.
And I'll even run it through the car wash
when I'm done.
Thank you so much.
It looks and sounds like a brand new car.
You're very welcome.
It smells delicious in here.
It sure does.
It's making me hungry.
Good morning.
Would you guys like to try one of our
famous cupcakes today?
That sounds amazing.
But we are here to order a cake.
Wonderful.
What kind of cake will you be ordering?
Are you celebrating a special occasion?
We are.
It's our wedding cake.
Congratulations.
That's so exciting.
We heard you make the best cakes in the
area, so we thought we would order it from you.
Well, thank you.
I appreciate it.
And I know you won't be disappointed.
When is the big day?
August 28th.
And how many people are you expecting?
We're inviting 100 people, but we assume
about 80 of them will actually attend.
Fantastic.
And do you have any flavors, you mind?
I love chocolate, and Alison loves
vanilla.
So we aren't sure what to order.
How about we do multiple layers?
Some can be chocolate, and some can be
vanilla.
I love that idea.
Me too.
Is buttercream icing okay?
Yes, we both love buttercream icing.
Perfect.
Do you want to sample some cake just to
make sure you like it?
Yes, please.
That sounds like a great idea.
Here you go.
One vanilla sample, and one chocolate
sample.
Oh my goodness.
This is delicious.
So good.
It melts in your mouth.
Thank you.
So I guess this means you're good with
your choices?
Definitely.
And what about a design?
Do you have anything in mind?
We were thinking some pink roses,
pearls, and ribbons in the icing.
Sounds great to me.
I drove a design and we can get the order
placed.
Thank you.
You're welcome.