Hey, Marcus. How's the job search going?
Not so great, actually. It's really frustrating.
Why is that?
I've submitted my resume and applications to over 10 places, and I've only gotten one interview.
That is rough. How did the interview go?
It was okay. I was nervous, and I think I spoke really fast.
Ultimately, they gave the job to someone with more experience.
Well, don't worry. In life, you have to pass failure to meet up with success.
Are there any other places hiring?
There are a few left on my list.
I'm still going to apply to as many jobs as possible, but there are a lot of other people looking for the same jobs.
There's a lot of competition these days for jobs in business.
I'll keep asking around to see if any of my other friends have openings in their companies.
Thanks. I appreciate it.
Relax. You will find the right job at the right time.
You speak two languages fluently.
There are plenty of companies that have great jobs for people who are bilingual.
Yeah, that's a big plus.
Thanks. I appreciate the support.
How about you guys? How's your work going?
For me, this past year has been incredible.
I have the job of my dreams.
The pay and perks they are offering are stupendous.
Perks like what?
Health insurance, free gym membership, paid time off, and company car.
I bet you are relishing every bit of it.
Yes, I am.
Well, the only downside is that I have very little free time left.
My office work keeps me busy all the time.
I am working even on the weekends.
I guess you can't really have your cake and eat it too.
Sometimes you have to make a few compromises.
That's right, but I can't complain.
I'm fine with it.
I love my job.
How about you, Nate?
My work has become topsy-turvy these days.
What exactly happened?
My boss is very demanding and not nice at all.
I have a lot on my plate these days.
I can understand.
You will sail through it like you always do.
I surely hope so.
Hey, Maggie, guess what?
I got a call about a job.
That's awesome, Marcus.
It's an accountant position, and I've got an interview tomorrow.
If I get the job, I'll be thrilled.
It's exactly what I've been looking for.
Okay, just try to look confident, and I'm sure you'll impress them.
Good luck.
I hope you get the job.
Thanks.
Good morning, Marcus.
I'm Julia.
Good morning.
Nice to meet you.
I am the finance department manager.
As you know, there is an open position in our team as a financial accountant,
and I need to fill this position as soon as possible.
This is an entry-level position, so we do not require a lot of experience.
We are going to train the new person.
That sounds great.
Can you tell me a little bit about yourself?
I have a degree in finance, and I am fluent in English and Spanish.
I worked as a part-timer in college for a startup agency.
I translated financial documents for them.
How long did you work for them?
About two years.
What are your strengths?
Why should we hire you?
Being a fresher, I think I'm very flexible and adaptive to learning new things.
I'm a hard-working person and a fast learner,
and I get along fine with people.
I'm highly organized and respectful.
Do you mind working long hours?
No, I don't.
Can you handle pressure?
Yes, I can.
In college, I took quite a few courses each semester,
while working at least 20 hours every week.
I handled that situation pretty well.
You sound really confident.
It has been nice talking to you.
We'll get back to you in a few days if you get selected for the job.
Thank you.
It has been a great pleasure coming here and talking to you.
Hello, I'm Marcus Brown.
I was hired as part of the finance team.
Welcome, Marcus.
We are so glad to have you working on our team.
I'm Danielle.
I'll be training you for the next few days.
Did you find us okay?
Yes, I did.
I came by car.
But it was a bit of a problem parking the car on the street.
You should have parked your car in the office's car park.
The entrance is at the back of the building.
I'll know next time.
Let me show you to your desk.
Here you go.
This is where you will be working.
Looks nice.
And this guy right next to you is Drew.
He is the financial controller of our team.
Drew, this is Marcus.
He's joining our team.
Welcome, Marcus.
We're glad to have you.
Thanks.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm excited to be here.
I'll take you now on a quick tour of the office.
Sounds good to me.
This is the break room.
We always have plenty of coffee and snacks available.
If you bring your lunch, you can put it in the fridge.
There's also a cafeteria on this floor where you can buy small snacks and drinks.
Where exactly is the cafeteria?
Just walk down the corridor in the front of us,
and at the end you'll find the cafeteria.
Oh, I see.
If you want a coffee, tea, can of Coke, or a bar of chocolate,
you can buy them on every floor from a vending machine.
When is break time, and how long does it last?
Break time lasts from 12 p.m. to 1 p.m.
There is also a gym next to the cafeteria,
if you want to work out on your break.
I would love that very much.
Here are the restrooms and the meeting rooms.
And over there is the CEO's office.
What is Mr. Easton like?
He's intimidating at first,
but he is really down to earth once you get to know him.
He has high expectations of all of his employees,
but he supports us and helps us succeed.
Our last stop is to pick up any supplies you need from the supply closet.
Who are those people over there?
Luciana is a newcomer just like you.
She's the one with long dark hair and blue dress.
And who's the guy talking on the phone?
Oh, you mean the one by the window?
In the blue shirt?
Ah, that's Ian.
He's the marketing director.
And that's Mike beside him.
He's responsible for the internal IT systems.
Okay, I'll try to remember all of this.
Don't worry about it.
For now, it's just good to put some faces to names.
We will have a team meeting at 9.30,
and I'll introduce you to everyone then.
This is the supply closet.
We have plenty of pens, pencils, staplers, notebooks, scissors, and more.
Whatever you need.
You can grab a few things and take them to your desk.
I think I'm all set now.
Thank you.
Hi, guys.
How's it going?
Everything is great.
What's new with you?
I am very well.
You look very happy.
What's the good news?
I have found a job as a financial accountant at a multinational company.
That's fantastic.
I'm so happy for you.
Way to go, man.
While I was searching for a job,
I came upon this exciting new opportunity.
My team is so supportive.
I feel like everyone gets along well
and helps each other out whenever it's needed.
It's a really friendly environment.
Congratulations on your lucky break.
Thanks a lot.
So, when can we expect a big treat?
Whenever you say.
How about lunch at Falcon's Nest Restaurant on Sunday?
That sounds good.
I will see you on Sunday then.
Thanks for watching.
And be sure to subscribe to our YouTube channel for more videos like this.