Oh
Dancing through springtime flowers and raisins on the sun catching what's the inflicts on your nose
Running through autumn leaves that float from trees on high with our love that is bigger than the sky
Guess how much I love you
I Know you could use it to keep the sun off you. Oh
It's perfect now you can go out in the hot sun
It does keep the sun off, but it is hard to keep on my head
especially when I do this
Thank you, it's the finest but it's not something that I need right now
Goodbye
Hello everyone, what will we do today? Let's roll through the long grass
collection of pebbles what about chasing this one down?
What do you think we should do little that brown hair
Do about what what do you think we should do today?
We could play with the ladybug. Oh
But it might get very thirsty last night it drank a whole drop of rainwater rainwater
That's it we could go and see if there are any new muddy paddles to slash in
What do you think this one up brown hair would you like to do that?
Yes, but I'm not sure the ladybug would like it. I might just keep an eye on it and see you all later
Don't be long this one up brown hair. All right, let's go and look for paddles. Let's go
Oh, but here comes little redwood fox
Want to play litter not brown hair?
It's too hot to do anything little redwood fox
That's a lovely cool breeze
Hi
I want to make a cool breeze too
Can you feel anything like a cool breeze? No
Try this leaf
Hmm that works, but it's not quite the same as having a special tail that can keep you cool in summer
My tail does something special in winter too want to see sure a cold day
It keeps me snugly and
See well that's really is a special tail
Little bit
Hello, are you cold little redwood fox?
He he he no I'm showing little not brown hair the special things I can do with my tail
Well, I have a special tail too. What's this?
Fantastic your tail is perfect for chasing maybe I can chase my tail
Oh, where is it hold on if I can just
Oh
Oh, that was a great really poorly. I wasn't trying to do a rolly poly little grey squirrel
I was trying to chase my tail. Why would you want to catch your tail?
Because it's fun
We've been showing this one up brown hair the special things we can do without tail
Whoa
How about this for special
Wow
That is special
My tail is very useful
Mine too
Sometimes I used it to say hello
He he he I use my tail to say
Boop
Oh what's wrong with that brown hair?
Oh I really wish I had a long tail that could do special things too
Why don't we make you a long tail?
Me with a long tail why not
Yeah, a long tail for me
Where did little film mask go?
I've got it
This piece of ivy will make you a lovely long tail
It'll be just like mine
What do you think?
It's just like yours little film mask
Chase it go on that will be fun
Whoops
It's a bit longer than your tail little film mask
A little bit too long
I know where to find a short to tell
Come on let's go
I'm short to tail
I like the sound of that
Boy for me
This spot will make a wonderful tail
Let's tie it on with the ivy
Great idea
Right about here
It's perfect
Oh thank you
It's wonderful
Go on try to switch it
It's a nice tail
But it doesn't switch very well
It's a bit
Flabby
I think you need a soft-up bushy tail
Soft-up and bushy
Like your tail?
Yes
We can make one with leaves
Yes let's
I know where to find just the right leaves
Come on let's go
Thank you
There
It really suits you
Look at me
I have a bushy tail
Try to switch it
It's a bit tickly
Try to wrap it around yourself like this
Oh no
Thanks everyone but
I'm not having much luck
With finding a new tail
We can't give up yet
Let's have another look
There must be something we can use for a special tail
Oh look up
Here
I'll look down here
I'll look up here
I guess I can look in here
Hello
Here you are
Big number and hair
Look
I found this
This will be perfect
Oh you have been busy
But what are these for?
For making me a long tail
A long tail?
Show him all the special things your long tails can do
Little field mouse you first
Okay
That looks like fun little field mouse
Look at my tail
Oh very nice little redwood fox
I can see your tail is very special too
Thank you
Hello being a brown hair
And hello little grey squirrel
What a great thing to be able to do
I say what you mean
Your friends have very special long tails
But your tail is special too
It is
I don't say how
It's too short
Do you see that bush over there?
Yes
Little field mouse
Would you mind running over there and waiting for a moment?
Sure
Where did she go?
I can't see her
We can't see her anymore
Okay
Maybe you could go and find her
And ask her to come back now
All right
And then can we see how special my tail is?
That's exactly what we'll do
Little not brown hair is easy to see
Because of his special white tail
But we can't see little field mouse at all
His tail always helps me find him
You do have a special tail little not brown hair
I do
It's white
And it's so easy to see
Really?
It's fantastic
Haha
Today
Brown and crunchy
A little creature
Bigger brown hair
He's having a snooze
Hello little green
Harry
creature.
Hello!
Tada!
It's me, little field mouse!
And that's not a little green hairy creature.
How do you know?
It's not a creature because it doesn't have any legs.
Some creatures don't have legs.
Like worms.
Well, it doesn't have eyes or a mouth either.
I think it's a something, not a someone.
It's a...
You don't know either?
No.
If it's a something, then I wonder what it's for.
There must be a reason it's here.
Haha.
Let's ask these are redwood flocks.
Great idea!
Looks lovely and scratchy.
I think it might be a special thing.
Little redwood flocks is used to scratch their backs.
A back scratcher?
Yes!
Why don't we try it out?
Like this?
Haha.
That's good.
Just up a bit.
A little bit harder.
Or it works!
Oh, I wonder if it would work for little brown hairs.
I don't think so.
Is it really a back scratcher?
Haha.
I don't know, but can you keep doing it?
I don't think it's a back scratcher at all.
Yeah.
Wow.
I think it's for making little feel nice.
Tola!
See how tall I am?
Oh, it's very tickly on my feet.
Haha.
I'm going to find your little brown hair.
Hmm?
Where did she go?
BOOM!
Haha.
You keep finding me too quickly.
Well, hide again.
I like finding.
I like hiding.
I'll start counting.
One caterpillar.
Oh, two caterpillars.
Three caterpillars.
Coming to find your little brown hair.
Hmm.
BOOM!
Hmm?
Hehe.
BOOM!
Uh-huh.
Hello?
What are you doing?
Playing?
A corn rolling.
We roll an acorn to the tree.
And whoever gets closest to the tree,
is that actually touching it?
Wings.
Do you want to play?
Yes, please.
I'll be really good at this.
I'll go first.
Look at what I thought of the game.
Okay.
Ah.
Yay!
Oh, be fast.
Okay.
Yay!
Ha-ha.
Go away, go away.
Little bit closer.
Yes!
Hehe.
My turn.
Oh.
Wow, that's the closest one yet.
I've got the closest to the tree.
I can get even closer.
Ha-ha.
Yay!
I win.
Oh.
You're not supposed to knock our acorns out of the way.
Yes, that's not fair.
Yes, it is.
Hold on, hold on.
Why don't we play a different game?
Like acorns stacking?
Huh?
We stack the acorns on top of each other.
Good idea.
That sounds fun.
Let's give it a go.
Hmm.
Oh.
I can only stack two acorns.
Me too.
This is hard.
I know.
But I'm gonna use acorns.
Oh, I got three.
Wow.
I'm going for four.
Oh.
You can do it, little fear of mouse.
You can do it.
Oh.
No.
Little redwood fox.
You startled me.
I didn't mean to.
I just get very excited sometimes.
It's all right.
Never mind.
Let's play a different game.
Can it be with acorns?
All right.
Let's play acorns growing.
What?
We just throw an acorn around?
Yes.
But you never know who is going to get the acorn next.
Like this.
I get it.
Oh, that sounds like a good game.
We'll all have to be on our toes.
Now spread out.
Here is the acorn around its nose.
Who gets it next?
Nobody knows.
Oh, yeah.
I caught it.
Whoa.
You almost strictly little fear of mouse.
Got it again.
Oh, my turn now.
Oh.
There's a redwood fox.
Oh, that's not how you play the game.
I could never catch that.
I'm sorry.
It was a bit high.
I got a bit carried away again.
I'll go and get the acorn.
It's no fun playing acorn games with little redwood fox.
Because she gets too excited and ruins everything.
Why don't we play without her?
She's through that acorn a long way away.
And you'll be away for quite some time.
Okay.
Oh.
She.
It's not right that we're not playing with little redwood fox.
But we can't play with her.
She gets too excited.
That's just who she is.
She can't help getting excited.
Does this mean we can never play with her again?
No.
We just have to play the right sort of game.
Oh.
I'm sorry for playing roughly.
When I get excited, I sometimes forget that I'm bigger and stronger than you.
Oh.
I'll try and think of you more when we're playing games.
Thank you little redwood fox.
We know you will.
And we'll try to think of games that we can all play.
Even very excited redwood foxes.
But what kind of game would that be?
I think I have an idea.
This is a much better game.
Three against one.
Perfect for fox.
He's bigger and stronger than us.
Now catch.
Whoa.
Go through.
I've got it.
Oh, I've got these.
Oh, oh, oh, hey.
I've got it.
What?
That was fun.
Let's do it again.
Guess how much I love you.
I hope you enjoyed this episode.
Don't forget to subscribe for more fun and adventure with me and all my friends.
See you next time.
Oh, thank you.