Oh.
Dancing through springtime flowers and
rays of summer sun, catching wet
snowflakes on your
nose, running through autumn leaves that
flots from trees on high with our
love that is bigger than the sky.
Guess how much I love you, guess how much
I love you, guess how much I love
you, guess Guess how much I love you.
Guess how much I love you.
So do you know what's Little
Yellow Quack really is?
Not really.
I just know he can't be a squirrel
because he doesn't have a pushy tail.
And squirrels don't quack.
Sorry, I haven't been much help.
Hey, look.
Is that her?
A lady bug?
Yes.
Wow.
Where did you get it?
It just flew onto me over there,
and now it seems to want to stay.
How pretty.
Look how small it is.
And it beautiful spots.
You are so lucky, little nut brown hair,
for it to stay with you.
Yes, I am.
Goodbye.
See you later.
Wake.
Hello.
Oh, hi.
Good morning, little gray squirrel.
Rise and shine.
Why?
It's very early and very
comfy up here in my tray.
Let me see.
Help me up, little nut brown hair.
It is comfy and wow.
I can see everything from up here.
My home's on top of the world.
That sounds amazing.
I'd like to see that.
What do you think?
Isn't it great?
Aren't you scared living
at the top of a tree?
Not a bit.
I wouldn't want to live anywhere else.
I wish we could all have
a really big A leaf.
Maybe we can.
A really, really big leaf.
Got it.
Yay.
It's huge.
Enormous.
Gigantic.
I've never seen these leaves before.
I have, but I've forgotten all about them.
And you helped me remember
letting up around here.
I did.
So let's play.
Come on.
I'm a grasshopper.
Watch me.
Did you see how high
that grasshopper jumped?
Almost as high as I can.
Is that you, little gray squirrel?
Come out and play.
We're trying to be brave.
Little gray squirrel, are you there?
Boo.
You can't scare me.
I'm much too brave.
Hello, brave field mouse.
And little nut brown hair.
Hello.
That's a big pile of nuts.
Yes.
Too many to carry up
the tree all by myself.
Oh, I know.
We could eat some for you,
so there'd be less to carry.
Thanks, but no, thanks.
If only I could get them to
that first branch, I'd be okay.
Oh, I know how to do it.
But how?
Together.
Ready?
There you are.
Thank you.
Last one.
Yay.
All done.
Thanks, little fior, mouse.
And thank you, little notran
here, for your clever idea.
Lucky, you are big and strong and brave
You're brave enough to carry me too.
Well, many little hands
do make light work.
See you later.
Bye.
Who's there?
Is that you, little gray Whirl.
Surprise.
I thought it was you.
Come up here, little not brown hair.
I want to show you something.
It's a bit high.
Let me help you up.
Wow.
The Meadow looks so
different from up here.
And look, there are cherries up here, too.
Oh.
Oh, look, a flowery field.
It's amazing what you
can see from up here.
I guess it is.
I'm used to it because
I'm up high in the tree every day.
Hello, up there.
How about dropping some of
those cherries down to me?
Good idea.
Here, Whoa.
Ha ha, got it.
Catch.
Here.
Hold on.
Wait a minute.
Oh, yeah, got it.
Hold on, slow, slow down.
Wait a minute.
Oh, got it.
Good catch, Bignard, brown hair.
Come back, you leaf.
Oh, what's going on?
Look at these lovely fresh acorns.
Another autumn treat.
Did that fall from the sky?
Hey.
Little gray squirrel, watch out.
Hello.
Oh, sorry.
Hello down there.
Good morning.
What are you up to?
I'm collecting as many acorns as I can.
They're ripe now, which means
we Winter is coming very soon.
Come and play in the leaves with us.
I'm much too busy
collecting food for winter.
Autumn is the busiest time for squirrels.
Listen, that brown hair?
Yes.
How do we make the most of the wind?
Look.
I'll get it.
Let me Let's chase it again.
We can't get them high enough to chase.
I think I know who can.
Okay.
So you want me to throw these off my tree?
Yes, please, little gray squirrel.
From the very top.
All right.
Be ready when I get up there.
We will be.
When he climbs that high, it
makes my tummy go all wibbly.
Don't worry.
Little gray squirrel is I'm afraid
for climbing up high in trees.
I know, but my tummy isn't
made for watching him.
Are you ready?
Ready.
Set.
Are you sure you're ready?
Ready?
He's not going to let the
seeds go right away, is he?
He always likes to have a bit of fun.
Still ready.
And we're still set.
On the count of three.
One, two.
Oh, I forgot.
What comes after two?
Three.
See, you weren't ready.