Oh
Dancing through springtime flowers and raisins on the sun catching what's the inflicts on your nose
Running through autumn leaves that float from trees on high with our love that is bigger than the sky
Guess I'm not try love you guess I'm not try love you guess how much I love you
Guess how much I love you
You who anybody home
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, right and shine. Sonny's on myself and the weather's fine
Hmm, what's up good morning with your field mask? Oh
Um, I mean field mice good morning
Wow such a big family
It must be snug and cozy inside your home
Very snug and cozy. I wouldn't want to live anywhere else
Here comes another leaf
It's coming straight to me
Oh, it didn't get it never mind little field mouse. I'll send you an extra special one
Something pretty something
What about that blossom?
Do you think little field mouse would like that?
Perfect what's perfect? What?
Just right there you'll see
It's pink
Thank you little brown hair. It's so pretty
It's a blossom. I'm going to keep it forever and ever
I'm winning
Look at all the sparkling stars
Yes, so many
Look some of them make pictures that one looks like a twinkling carrot
Yes, and over there a twinkling now
Well there with a long shiny tail made of twinkling stars
Come on, let's touch one
Oh, yeah, we need to be higher
Go up on your tiptoes this and that brown hair. I'm nearly there
What are we looking for? Well, we're not exactly looking for it. Oh
Well, smelling for it. What does it smell like? It smells fresh, sweet and pretty
Oh, I know that smell. Yay! I wait for me
Smell this blue flowery on that brown hair. Oh
See sweet and pretty
Am I right? You are right. It is sweet and pretty but
But it's not exactly the smell we are searching for
I'll take this one back so big nut brown hair can smell how lovely it is
Okay, so what can we smell next? Oh little white flowers
Oh, do you come and smell them?
Hmm sweet and orangey and a little bit like the smell we're searching for but
But not the exact one right
For big nut brown hair
He follows you everywhere everywhere
He followed me all the way to visit you little film house
Hello, what's your name?
That's all he ever says. I think he's too young to talk
Hmm do you know what he is? I know he isn't a hair
Well, I think he's a oh, I know he's probably
Oh
Well, whatever he is he can't be a mouse because he doesn't have whiskers like me
We can't call him whatever he is he needs a proper name. I know. I know we can call him little
Yes
Hello, uh-huh. I don't know
Hmm you've got to have a name everyone does
That's it what we'll call him little yellow quick. Yeah perfect
What do you think of that little yellow crack
He I think he likes it
Around and around
Open your eyes
What do you say a orphan
And she's singing
I turn again around and around
Can you see anything from down there?
Yes
Blue bird is making a nest. Oh, so she is
That looks like fun if we had our nest we can play it together
Why don't we build one it doesn't look that hard
Yes, let's do it. I'll get some leaves and I'll go and find some twigs and sticks
Oh
Sorry little field mouse it's okay little nut brown hair
Now what do we do?
Hmm well, I suppose we put them together in some sort of nest shape
I'll put this here and that's it and make it kind of roundish
There our very own list
Wait, I've got one leaf left
Oh
We didn't make it strong enough then let's try again
There that should be stronger
Yeah
It's much stronger
But it's still not quite strong enough then let's try again
There do you think it's strong enough let's try
Oh
It is strong enough
Hurray
Well, what do you think of our nest? It's a bit
itchy
Yes the sticks and twigs are
Very polky and prickly and scratchy and stickly
We need to find something
Soft to line the nest with
To make it more comfortable I know just the thing
A little bush
Makes that nest even more prickly
Not the prickly scissors or use a soft down
Feel how soft it is like a feather
I
It tickles
I told you it was soft like a feather
This should stop our nest being so prickly and polky
You're right our nest isn't prickly now it's
tickling yes
Can't use the nest
Because of me
All the time
We've never get me playing done
Little field mouse where are you
There you are
I like that pretty flower
Thank you little nut brown hair it's a lovely color isn't it and it smells so sweet
Oh butterflies like it too
Oh
Isn't that pretty thank you little redwood fox see lighter that butterfly really likes you hello little grey squirrel
I think it just likes the flower
It looks so sweet
Thank you
Bye bye
That was very kind of them to say such nice things about me
Well having a flower and a butterfly does make you very special really
Let's make you special too me how by getting a flower and a butterfly for you too oh yes
There are some beautiful flowers here
Try this one
Ah here butterflies come to the flower
Shhh little nut brown hair you'll scare them away oops sorry
You have to be still
Am I still enough perfectly
Then why on to any butterflies come into the flower
Maybe there aren't any butterflies around here
Maybe they just don't like this kind of flower
Hmm maybe I'm just not special I'm sure you are
Hmm
Oh ladybug
It tickles
I didn't do anything it just landed on me just like the butterfly landed on me
Now it doesn't want to leave me alone
See you are special after all is on that brown hair I guess I am
Oh
Sorry little field mouse I was enjoying the things of spring me too
Do you know what my favorite spring thing is the colors in winter everything is white and gray
But in spring look around you how many different colors can you see
Hmm
Oh green grass yellow flowers and blue flowers and green leaves
Huh blue sky blue bird
Hello little field map hello little nut brown hair what a lovely day
Oh orange butterfly
Not brown hey
Brown field mouse
Little field mouse you startled me
Haha
Yes, I did
I you had no idea I was there
That's because I am on a very important hunt what for yummy berries that I was saving for breakfast
Then your hunt is over it is yes look what I just jumped out of
A bush full of yummy blueberries
Oh the berries I lost were red
But these are still very delicious I ate some this morning with my family
Why not have this for breakfast instead
Thanks, but I want to special red berries
Beed nut brown hair said they were his favorite berries of all
Oh in that case I might just eat some more of these
Just to see if they're still delicious
They are in fact they're very very delicious
Can you see any blue yet
No
But there are lots of other lovely colors
The flower smell lovely
Oh
It's a ladybug
Is it blue?
Two reds
It's flying fast
Come back little red ladybug
Come back little nut brown hair
Woo
Me
Look at this flowers this one up brown hair
Uh-uh
Two yellow
I can't see anything that's blue
I see them I see them too
Wow
Blue flowers oh yeah blue flowers
And they smell blue too
The dawns of the blue bell
Very young
Don
Hello, what are you doing?
Finding beautiful blue things for beegna brown hair
Look something else that's blue
They are sparkly blue gems
Oh
They're broken shells from my exit have just hatched blue eggshells from a blue bird
Oh, so are your babies now blue bird
They're right here
Hello
Chuk chuk chuk chuk chuk chuk chuk chuk chuk chuk chuk chuk chuk chuk
Nice time for chirping
Yes time to find more blue things I know follow me
Yay
Goodbye
Guess how much I love you
I hope you enjoyed this episode.
Don't forget to subscribe for more fun and adventure with me and all my friends.
See you next time.
Oh thank you.