I never graduated from college and this is
the closest I've ever gotten to a college graduation.
Today I want to tell you three stories
from my life.
That's it.
No big deal.
Just three stories.
The first story is about connecting the
dots.
I dropped out of Reed College after the
first six months but then stayed around as a drop in for another 18 months or so before I really quit.
So why'd I drop out?
It started before I was born.
My biological mother was a young unwed
graduate student and she decided to put me up for adoption.
She felt very strongly that I should be
adopted by college graduates so everything was all set for me to be adopted at birth by a lawyer and his wife.
Except that when I popped out they decided
at the last minute that they really wanted a girl.
So my parents who were on a waiting list
got a call in the middle of the night asking,
we've got an unexpected baby boy.
Do you want him?
They said, of course.
My biological mother found out later that
my mother had never graduated from college and that my father had never graduated from high school.
She refused to sign the final adoption
papers.
She only relented a few months later when
my parents promised that I would go to college.
This was the start in my life.
And 17 years later I did go to college but
I naively chose a college that was almost as expensive as Stanford and all of my working class parents' savings were being spent on my college tuition.
After six months I couldn't see the value
in it.
I had no idea what I wanted to do with my
life and no idea how college was going to help me figure it out.
And here I was spending all the money my
parents had saved their entire life.
So I decided to drop out and trust that it
would all work out okay.
It was pretty scary at the time but
looking back it was one of the best decisions I ever made.
The minute I dropped out I could stop
taking the required classes that didn't interest me and begin dropping in on the ones that looked far more interesting.
It wasn't all romantic.
I didn't have a dorm room so I slept on
the floor in friends rooms.
I returned coat bottles for the five -cent
deposits to buy food with.
And I would walk the seven miles across
town every Sunday night to get one good meal a week at the Hari Krishna Temple.
I loved it.
And much of what I stumbled into by
following my curiosity and intuition turned out to be priceless later on.
Let me give you one example.
Read college at that time offered perhaps
the best calligraphy instruction in the country.
Throughout the campus every poster every
label on every drawer was beautifully hand calligraphed.
Because I had dropped out and didn't have
to take the normal classes I decided to take a calligraphy class to learn how to do this.
I learned about serif and sans serif
typefaces about varying the amount of space between different letter combinations about what makes great typography great.
It was beautiful historical artistically
subtle in a way that science can't capture and I found it fascinating.
None of this had even a hope of any
practical application in my life.
But ten years later when we were designing
the first Mac and Tosh computer it all came back to me.
And we designed it all into the Mac.
It was the first computer with beautiful
typography.
If I had never dropped in on that single
course in college the Mac would have never had multiple typefaces or proportionally spaced fonts.
And since Windows just copied the Mac it's
likely that no personal computer would have them.
If I had never dropped out I would have
never dropped in on that calligraphy class and personal computers might not have the wonderful typography that they do.
Of course it was impossible to connect the
dots looking forward when I was in college.
But it was very very clear looking
backwards ten years later.
Again you can't connect the dots looking
forward.
You can only connect them looking
backwards.
So you have to trust that the dots will
somehow connect in your future.
You have to trust in something,
your gut, destiny, life, karma, whatever.
Because believing that the dots will
connect down the road will give you the confidence to follow your heart even when it leads you off the well -worn path.
And that will make all the difference.
My second story is about love and loss.
I was lucky.
I found what I loved to do early in life.
Was and I started Apple in my parents'
garage when I was 20.
We worked hard and in ten years Apple had
grown from just the two of us in a garage into a $2 billion company with over 4,000 employees.
We just released our finest creation, the
Macintosh a year earlier and I just turned 30.
And then I got fired.
How can you get fired from a company you
started?
Well,
as Apple grew we hired someone who I
thought was very talented to run the company with me.
And for the first year or so things went
well.
But then our visions of the future began
to diverge and eventually we had a falling out.
When we did our board of directors sided
with him.
And so at 30 I was out and very publicly
out.
What had been the focus of my entire adult
life was gone and it was devastating.
I really didn't know what to do for a few
months.
I felt that I had let the previous
generation of entrepreneurs down that I had dropped the baton as it was being passed to me.
I met with David Packard and Bob Nois and
tried to apologize for screwing up so badly.
I was a very public failure and I even
thought about running away from the valley.
But something slowly began to dawn on me.
I still loved what I did.
The turn of events at Apple had not
changed that one bit.
I'd been rejected but I was still in love.
And so I decided to start over.
I didn't see it then but it turned out
that getting fired from Apple was the best thing that could have ever happened to me.
The heaviness of being successful was
replaced by the lightness of being a beginner again, less sure about everything.
It freed me to enter one of the most
creative periods of my life.
During the next five years I started a
company named Next,
another company named Pixar,
and fell in love with an amazing woman who
would become my wife.
Pixar went on to create the world's first
computer animated feature film, Toy Story, and is now the most successful animation studio in the world.
In a remarkable turn of events,
Apple bought Next and I returned to Apple
and the technology we developed at Next is at the heart of Apple's current renaissance.
And Lauren and I have a wonderful family
together.
I'm pretty sure none of this would have
happened if I hadn't been fired from Apple.
It was awful tasting medicine but I guess
the patient needed it.
Sometimes life, sometimes life's going to
hit you in the head with a brick.
Don't lose faith.
I'm convinced that the only thing that
kept me going was that I loved what I did.
You've got to find what you love and that
is as true for work as it is for your lovers.
Your work is going to fill a large part of
your life and the only way to be truly satisfied is to do what you believe is great work.
And the only way to do great work is to
love what you do.
If you haven't found it yet, keep looking
and don't settle.
As with all matters of the heart, you'll
know when you find it.
And like any great relationship, it just
gets better and better as the years roll on.
So keep looking, don't settle.
My third story is about death.
When I was 17, I read a quote that went
something like,
if you live each day as if it was your
last, someday you'll most certainly be right.
It made an impression on me.
And since then, for the past 33 years,
I've looked in the mirror every morning
and asked myself, if today were the last day of my life, what I want to do, what I am about to do today.
And whenever the answer has been no for
too many days in a row,
I know I need to change something.
Remembering that I'll be dead soon is the
most important tool I've ever encountered to help me make the big choices in life.
Because almost everything,
all external expectations, all pride, all
fear of embarrassment or failure,
these things just fall away in the face of
death,
leaving only what is truly important.
Remembering that you are going to die is
the best way I know to avoid the trap of thinking you have something to lose.
You are already naked.
There is no reason not to follow your
heart.
About a year ago, I was diagnosed with
cancer.
I had a scan at 7.30
in the morning and it clearly showed a
tumor on my pancreas.
I didn't even know what a pancreas was.
The doctors told me this was almost
certainly a type of cancer that is incurable and that I should expect to live no longer than three to six months.
My doctor advised me to go home and get my
affairs in order,
which is doctor's code for prepare to die.
It means to try and tell your kids
everything.
You thought you'd have the next 10 years
to tell them in just a few months.
It means to make sure everything is
buttoned up so that it will be as easy as possible for your family.
It means to say your goodbyes.
I live with that diagnosis all day.
Later that evening, I had a biopsy where
they stuck an endoscope down my throat,
through my stomach and into my intestines,
put a needle into my pancreas and got a
few cells from the tumor.
I was sedated, but my wife who was there
told me that when they viewed the cells under a microscope,
the doctor started crying because it
turned out to be a very rare form of pancreatic cancer that is curable with surgery.
I had the surgery, and thankfully,
I'm fine now.
This was the closest I've been to facing
death,
and I hope it's the closest I get for a
few more decades.
Having lived through it, I can now say
this to you with a bit more certainty than when death was a useful but purely intellectual concept.
No one wants to die.
Even people who want to go to heaven don't
want to die to get there.
And yet, death is the destination we all
share.
No one has ever escaped it.
And that is, as it should be, because
death is very likely the single best invention of life.
It's life's change agent.
It clears out the old to make way for the
new.
Right now, the new is you.
But someday, not too long from now, you
will gradually become the old and be cleared away.
Sorry to be so dramatic,
but it's quite true.
Your time is limited, so don't waste it
living someone else's life.
Don't be trapped by dogma, which is living
with the results of other people's thinking.
Don't let the noise of others' opinions
drown out your own inner voice.
And most important, have the courage to
follow your heart and intuition.
They somehow already know what you truly
want to become.
Everything else is secondary.
When I was young,
there was an amazing publication called
The Whole Earth Catalog, which was one of the bibles of my generation.
It was created by a fellow named Stuart
Brand,
not far from here in Menlo Park,
and he brought it to life with his poetic
touch.
This was in the late 60s, before personal
computers and desktop publishing,
so it was all made with typewriters,
scissors, and Polaroid cameras.
It was sort of like Google in paperback
form 35 years before Google came along.
It was idealistic, overflowing with neat
tools and great notions.
Stuart and his team put out several issues
of The Whole Earth Catalog,
and then, when it had run its course,
they put out a final issue.
It was the mid -1970s, and I was your age.
On the back cover of their final issue was
a photograph of an early morning country road,
the kind you might find yourself
hitchhiking on if you were so adventurous.
Beneath it were the words, stay hungry,
stay foolish.
It was their farewell message as they
signed off.
Stay hungry, stay foolish.
And I have always wished that for myself.
And now, as you graduate to begin a new,
I wish that for you.
Stay hungry, stay foolish.
Thank you all very much.