I'm Peppa Pig, this is my little brother George, this is Mummy Pig, and this is Daddy Pig.
Peppa Pig!
Bubbles!
Peppa and George are drinking orange juice.
What noisy little piggies!
George, look at all the tiny bubbles!
I can make bigger bubbles!
Peppa is blowing bubbles in her drink.
George wants to blow bubbles too.
Peppa, George, you really shouldn't play with your food!
Sorry Daddy!
Peppa, if you like bubbles, why don't you play with your bubble mixture?
Yes, my bubble mixture!
George, let's blow bubbles in the garden!
Peppa is showing George how to blow bubbles.
First, dip the stick in the mixture.
Then, take a big breath and blow.
Bubbles!
George, now it's your turn.
Dip the stick in the mixture.
Hold it up.
Take a big breath and blow.
George is trying really hard, but he is running out of breath.
Achoo!
George, you didn't blow hard enough.
I know a way George can make bubbles.
Dip the stick in the mixture, then lift it up and wave it around.
Bubbles!
It's even better if you run along.
Wait for me!
George is having fun making bubbles.
And Peppa is having fun popping them.
I love bubbles!
Oh dear, the bubble mixture is all used up.
Daddy! Mummy!
There's no more bubble mixture.
Don't worry, Peppa. I have an idea.
Mummy Pig, bring me a bucket, please.
Yes, Daddy Pig.
Peppa, bring me some soap.
George, bring me my old tennis racket.
A bucket, some soap, a tennis racket.
What is Daddy Pig doing?
First, I need some water.
Then the soap.
And now the tennis racket, please.
Thank you.
Now watch this.
Wow!
Daddy Pig has made his own bubble mixture.
Come on, everyone.
Be careful, Daddy Pig. Don't slip and fall.
I'll be fine.
Are you okay, Daddy Pig?
Yes, I'm fine.
Wow!
Daddy Pig has made the biggest bubble ever.
Oh dear, I've spilled all my bubble mixture.
Now we can't make any more bubbles.
But we can play jumping in muddy puddles.
Look!
Daddy Pig's bubble mixture has made a big muddy puddle.
Peppa loves jumping up and down in muddy puddles.
Look!
The bubble mixture has made the puddle all bubbly.
Peppa loves jumping up and down in muddy bubbly puddles.
Everyone loves jumping up and down in muddy bubbly puddles.
Peppa Pig.