I'm Peppa Pig.
This is my little brother George.
This is Mummy Pig.
And this is Daddy Pig.
Peppa Pig!
Emily Elephant!
Peppa and her friends are going to playgroup today.
The children each have their own hook to hang their coats on.
Today we have a new pupil, Emily Elephant.
Hello Emily!
Hello!
Emily is a bit shy.
Who would like to show Emily where to hang her coat?
Me!
We just need one.
Peppa, can you show Emily where to hang her coat?
We just need one. Peppa, can you show Emily where to hang her coat?
Yes, Madam Gazelle.
We each have our own coat hooks.
This one is for you, Emily.
Emily is hanging her coat on her very own coat hook.
Now Emily, what would you like to do today?
Painting, clay or building blocks?
Hmm, I don't know.
Maybe building blocks.
Hmm, I don't know. Maybe building blocks.
And everyone else?
Painting, clay or building blocks?
And everyone else? Painting, clay or building blocks?
Building blocks!
My goodness!
Building blocks are popular today.
Everyone wants to sit next to Emily Elephant.
Emily, you put one block on top of another.
Like this.
Emily, you put one block on top of another. Like this.
It's better if you put them side by side.
No!
This way, Emily.
Meow!
This is the right way, Emily.
Nay!
No, Emily.
Like this.
You are all being very helpful.
But Emily, how would you play with the blocks?
Um, I'm not very sure.
I might do it like this.
Um, I'm not very sure. I might do it like this.
Wow!
Emily Elephant is good at building blocks.
It is playtime.
Hooray!
Emily, would you like to play outside with the others?
Yes, please.
Can someone show Emily where we play?
Yes, Madam Gazelle.
At playtime, Peppa and her friends play in the school garden.
Can't catch me!
What a lot of noise!
Let's see who is the loudest.
OK, I'll go first.
Squeak!
Squeak! Squeak!
That was quite loud.
Now it is Zoe Zebra's turn.
Now Susie Sheep.
Now Danny Dog.
That was very loud.
My turn!
Peppa is the loudest.
Emily, you try!
I'm not too sure.
Please, Emily!
OK, I'll try.
Ah!
My goodness!
That was loud!
Wow!
Do it again!
Ah!
Emily is not shy anymore.
Ha!
Emily, would you like to play my favourite game?
What is your favourite game?
Jumping in muddy puddles!
That's my favourite game too!
This looks like fun.
Yippee!
This looks like fun. Yippee!
Emily, have you enjoyed your first day at our playgroup?
Yes, Madame Gazelle.
And I see you've made lots of new friends.
Yes!
Emily Elephant is my friend.
And Emily is my friend.
And mine.
Emily, who do you like best?
Um, I like Susie and Danny and Zoe.
And Rebecca and Pedro and Peppa.
Peppa Pig.
Tou fair and do,