I'm Peppa Pig.
This is my little brother George.
This is Mummy Pig.
And this is Daddy Pig.
Peppa Pig.
Polly's Holiday.
Granny and Grandpa Pig are going on holiday.
They are bringing Polly Parrot to Peppa's house, so Peppa and George can look after her.
Hello, everyone.
Hello, Grandpa Pig.
Hello, Granny Pig.
Polly is very excited about her holiday with Peppa and George.
Hello, Polly.
Polly Parrot copies everything that is said.
What's in Polly's suitcase, Granny?
This is Polly's food.
George, can you guess what Polly likes to eat best?
Chocolate cake.
No, not chocolate cake.
Polly likes birdseed.
Birdseed!
Can I feed her, Granny Pig?
Can I feed her?
Can I feed her, Granny Pig? Can I feed her?
Yes.
It's very important not to give Polly too much food.
Yes, Grandpa Pig.
Grandpa, can Polly come out of the cage?
Yes.
But you must keep all the doors and windows closed so Polly doesn't fly away.
Yes, Grandpa Pig.
Goodbye, Peppa.
Goodbye, George.
Goodbye, Granny Pig.
Goodbye, Grandpa Pig.
Would you like a cup of tea?
George has got Polly's birdseed.
George, that is too much birdseed.
Polly will grow very big and burst like a balloon.
Pop!
Burst like a balloon!
What's that noise?
Ice cream!
Hooray!
Ice cream! Hooray!
Oh, dear.
George has forgotten to close the door.
Oh, dear. George has forgotten to close the door.
Ice cream!
Ice cream! Ice cream!
It is Miss Rabbit, the ice cream lady.
Hello, Mummy Pig.
Hello, Miss Rabbit.
Four ice creams, please.
Thank you, Miss Rabbit.
George, you forgot to close the door.
Polly will have flown away.
Don't worry, Peppa.
I'm sure Polly's still inside.
Polly's not here.
Oh.
We've lost Polly.
Grandpa and Granny are going to be very sad.
Maybe we should try the garden.
Look!
What's that?
Look! What's that?
What has Mummy Pig seen in the garden?
It's Polly!
Hooray!
It's Polly! Hooray!
But, Daddy, how are we going to get Polly down from the tree?
Don't worry, Peppa.
I'll rescue Polly.
Come on, Polly.
Would you like a cup of tea?
Oh, no.
Polly has flown higher up the tree.
Oh, dear.
Be careful, Daddy.
Don't fall out of the tree like you always do.
Don't worry, Peppa.
I'll be very careful.
Come on, Polly.
Birdseed!
I wonder where George is going.
George has got Polly's birdseed.
Polly loves to eat birdseed.
Ah!
George has got Polly down from the tree.
Hooray!
What's that noise?
Daddy Pig's mobile phone is ringing.
What?
Oh!
Hello?
Oh, Granny Pig.
Hello, Daddy Pig.
Please, may I talk to Polly?
Yes, of course.
Hello, Polly.
Are you having a nice holiday?
Oh!
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Whoa!
Oh!
Peppa Pig!
You